In this video, I challenged myself to
see if I could grow just 0.1 Solana by
trading Solana meme coins for exactly 1
hour. It definitely didn't go as
planned. We hit some great trades, made
some solid profits, even lost the entire
balance at one point, then we reloaded,
and then caught a coin that completely
changed the outcome. But, this isn't
just a challenge video. As we go through
every trade, I'll show you exactly what
I look for before buying a meme coin,
the biggest mistakes that cost me money,
how to avoid common vamps, common rugs,
and how to give yourself the best chance
of picking the right coin. If you've
ever wanted to start trading Solana meme
coins, but didn't know where to begin,
this video should save you a lot of time
and a lot of money as well. So, yeah,
let's get into it. So, the rules are
simple. I have 1 hour to trade meme
coins with only 0.1 Solana. I just
started the timer. I have 1 hour. I did
this experiment a while ago, and it went
quite decent, but right now I've only
given myself 1 hour to see if I can make
something work. This is not bad. This is
not bad. This is not bad at all. Buy
this with 0.005.
Boost coin is good, but it seems like it
has been done before. So, this is a gap
dev. Hmm, this could be not half bad. It
is kind of pumping. We're already up
30%, which is not really a lot. Oh, I
bought the wrong amount. Oh, hell no,
bro. I didn't buy with enough. I put an
extra zero in, bro. We would have been
up a decent chunk. Anyone want to buy
this [__] though? But, I'm going to
wait for a dip. Please dip, just a
little bit. Just I want just want a
little dip. Bang, there we go. Oh my
god, straight to zero it feels. I'm
going to buy a little bit more. So,
we're back at our 10K entry mark.
[music]
I do believe that this could send if
This is a slight bit up in profits
because Jack Du Well just bought. I'm
going to sell 50% right here just
because it's a slight bit of profits,
and I'm really not certain on when Jack
Du Well would dump on this [__] so I'm
going to keep on holding this cuz if it
hits migration, it would be really,
really good. Anyways, what I'm going to
do is going to set a limit order in
profit, so even if this thing goes down,
I don't really end up losing money on
this coin. If anything, I just want to
make money, so there we go. Till then,
we have 0.06 Solana. Let's just go look
at more coins. This
is not that bad. Could be a good buy,
but the volume just does not look good
on this. Willy just bonded. I don't I
don't know if his name is Willy though.
That's the thing I want to check. I
don't want to close out the timer on
accident. Never stop scamming, you know,
okay, bro. How Is his name really Willy?
Cuz if it is, then this could be a
sender. Oh, no, we had a chance to buy
that 5K. This could have been a 2X. Ah,
this This feels so bad when you fade a
runner. Cuz if I bought it right here,
it would have been up 2X already. What
is Boost up to?
Oh, Shaq Wall has sold. Okay, we might
be getting out of this with only 0.01
Solana made, but I want this thing to
bond, to be honest. Disabled Goldfish.
You know, this could have been good if I
spotted it earlier. It's okay, let's
keep on searching for more. Willy is up
20%. You know what, that wasn't a bad
buy at all. Right now, we have a 100%
win rate on our coins. Going to take 25%
profit right here. We only bought this
thing with two and a half dollars. Boost
is just doing its thing for now. What is
this? Meow Pin. That is not bad. We need
to buy Meow Pin. I'm selling this.
Actually, I'm selling the entirety of
Willy. Let me get into Meow Pin. Meow
Pin looks good. I'm going to be aping
0.05 Solana in this. Stop blasting, of
course, cuz if this is real, this could
go to 100K. Boys, the lesson is always
wait for a dip. Always do, okay? I do
believe if the story is real, this could
send up to at least 100K. We do have
enough volume because the wheelchair
fish just did what we want this coin to
do. We bought this with about three and
a half dollars or 0.05 Solana, which is
half our balance. And I am down to DCA a
little bit more in this. I'm going to be
buying around 27K if it gets to that
point. Yeah, that is enough. Let's buy
here. Hopefully, this dip gets eaten up.
It all depends on how real this is,
which to be honest I haven't done my
research yet. I should probably do that.
meowopen.info and here it is.
meowopen_info.
Okay, the coin seems to be real. Okay,
but the price does not reflect, which is
not really good. This could be the end
of the challenge right here. We need
this to go back up. I cannot open TikTok
to see if the account is really funny or
is it not funny cuz TikTok is banned
from where I'm from. See, that is the
thing. That is what I'm talking about.
If you buy late into these coins,
people who buy here are going to sell on
you. So,
getting to your break-even price is very
very hard unless the coin is absolutely
phenomenal, which I do think this is.
So, I'm just going to keep on holding,
be patient, and let's wait to see what
happens. I'm going to look for more
opportunities whenever this coin dies.
I'm going to sell my dust and yeah.
Guys, so I'm just going to go over the
mistakes that we made in this coin.
First of all, we bought too [__] high
before the confirmation of the account
claiming the fees. Then it started
dumping straight up. So, this was a
farm. Although I was really limited here
because TikTok is banned in my country
and if I open a VPN right now, Axiom
would stop working properly, so I could
not do that. But whenever you see these
kind of coins, always open TikTok, look
at what the thing is about, and then ape
into something, not blindly like me.
Just for the sake of this video, I'm
going to be depositing 0.1 SOL again to
see if we can run this up. Okay, boys,
so we have reloaded the balance and we
have 0.1 SOL into this coin. This is
about a person who just got hit by a
Molotov.
We have about 31 minutes remaining.
Okay, now that is brutal, bro. What did
I just watch?
And are we about to make money on this
coin? I don't know. The narrative is not
that strong, bro. If it wasn't for this
challenge, I would have gotten out just
about right here. Just Just saw this
coin called dead dog in a helmet. This
sounds really really fun. I'm just going
to ape in 0.05. Let's just see what
happens here. Oh, that is a big candle.
This is really funny meme. The dog in
helmet. Yeah, yeah, now this is good.
This is good. I wish we had more Solana.
But we sadly do not.
Which is all good. This is a good coin.
I feel like this could bond. Since we
really need this, I'm just going to hold
this thing until bond and see what
happens. If we lose this, we're going to
call this challenge a fail, bro. And
we're going to try it again someday
later. Okay, we're already up 2x on the
coin, which is really really good. This
is surely a bonder, bro. I'm not selling
until this thing bonds or goes to zero.
I'm fine with either. We'll call this
challenge a fail if it is bad. Okay,
there is a vamp. I don't like that. Oh
my god, this bro, vamping is such a big
problem in the trenches. Would we be
successfully vamped on this? Cuz the
real name is Argos, but DEH just sounds
funnier, you know? Or am I tripping? Is
this Earl bought into my coin, which is
good. I really do not like the fact that
there are two coins running with the
same [__] narrative. But quite
honestly, DEH is a better name. I really
don't care what the dog is called. DEH
is just a better name, better memeable
name. I'm just going to be holding this
coin. Though, it is losing the vamp
race, if I'm being honest. Oh, this is
not a good look for us. Whoever builds a
vamp-free launchpad, we will all switch
off of Pump Fun because this is just not
it, you know? We do not need two coins
running with the same narrative, ever.
Kind of hoping Argos dies off and DEH is
the one that wins. That does prove there
is enough volume for us to bond a coin.
And I really think DEH is going to be
the one that bonds. Bang, there we go.
Conviction pays off. Want to take about
50% profits right here. That is a
successful trade already. I would want
to wait for this to bond. This is good.
Is Argos catching volume again? Who's
this, Yianni? My god, Yianni, you're so
stupid. Just buy the real coin. Let's
just look at our coin. Let's not feed
energy into Argos.
Cuz no one wants that coin to bond. No
one does, okay? It's Day all the way. We
have about 25 minutes left. Ooh, that is
a big dip. What I'm going to do is I'm
going to buy this dip as well. Oh, I
don't have enough money. Let me quickly
just buy this dip. There we go. Now,
there are so many vamps coming out, bro.
This is cancer. Let's just focus on our
coin. I do believe that this will be the
one that bonds. Not going to bother
looking at other coins cuz Day is the
real meme, baby. Come on. Okay, we're
finally seeing some good buys. Boys, I
can't lie. If this bonds, this could go
parabolic, bro. I could see this hitting
50k, 60k, and if we're lucky, even 100k
because there is definitely enough
volume here. Okay, so we basically 2x
our balance in a single trade. I am
going to be selling about 25% pre-bond.
You guys also need to keep in mind the
market sentiment right now since in the
new pairs, there is not really anything
good.
And Day is the only coin that feels like
it could pump. Unless, what is this?
Okay, the market sentiment is kind of
dying because we have one more potential
bonder in Tim. I'm not going to focus on
other coins because we don't really have
much balance. Even if I do go ahead and
buy that coin with 0.01 Solana, it
10x's, we don't really make that much
money. I should have sold 25% of my
position. That is not really ideal if
I'm being honest. Going to be taking
another clip of 15%.
Attempting transaction, brother.
Yo, let me sell, boy. Yo, is Axi really
that bad? Boys, you got to switch to
GMGN. Do we really have to switch to
GMGN now? Okay, there we go. Just some
network issue. That is all good. No way
all the volume's flowing in here instead
of there. Anyways, let's just look at
this. ArcBot again, how much? $39? Not
ideal. This is about to bond, boys.
This is really just about to bond.
What I'm going to do is set a limit
order for a sell right here. So, even if
it dumps, we end up walking away with a
decent amount of money. All we need to
do is not sell. Come on, boys. You held
this [__] for so long. Why would you
sell now? Just let it bond. Okay, there
we go. We just bonded. I'm just going to
keep on holding this [__] Like, send
this [__] to 50k right now. I kind of
like the fact that Art is buying again.
Oh, big candle. Big candle, baby. Come
on, the volume's finally flowing in into
this coin. I should honestly start
taking some clips. There we go.
Attempting transaction again. Boys, I
can't lie. Axium is slow as hell. Switch
to GMGN now. You guys might be wondering
that why are you trading on Axium if it
is really just that bad? The real answer
is I just had that much Solana in this
wallet and I didn't feel like trading on
GMGN, which is my usual platform where I
trade on. I thought why not give Axium a
chance, but never again, bro. This [__]
is ass. Quite honestly, we're not
getting the volume that I was expecting
we would get when we migrate. So, I'm
just going to sell 50% right here. And
even if this coin goes to zero, we've
made 50% on our portfolio in just under
an hour, bro. We still have 13 minutes
to spare. Oh my god, what is that
candle? I sold too fast, boys. Okay.
That is absurd. That is an absurd
candle. Boys, if it didn't clip at all,
we would have been at 0.4 Solana in
profits.
Or 0.5 Solana in profit. We still have
about 12 minutes remaining. So, I'm just
going to let this coin cook and go on to
pulse and see what is happening. Whoop.
Uh, we're kind of dumping down, but I do
believe this dip will be eaten up
really, really fast. So, I'm not really
worried. If anything, I'm just going to
set a stop loss down here. And here we
sell 0.4 Solana. And no matter what
happens now, we will be making 2x on our
starting balance in just under an hour.
There we go. That is a very big buy from
who is that? Oh, cooker bot. Oh, no.
This could go to 100k now. We still
don't have to sell. We have 10 minutes
remaining. We just going to chill in
this coin. Guys, we have some balance to
play with now, but we're not going to be
forcing trades as that is the worst
thing that you guys can do. Just sit on
your hands, protect the money that
you've made, don't ape in something that
you don't really like at all. Like Dog
in Hat has had his run. So, what I'm
going to do, I'm going to sell 100% of
my balance right here. There we go. That
is a very successful trade. It just took
one trade to take us from 0.1 Solana to
0.245,
which is a success in my book. And now,
I'm just going to close the timer right
here because we have 6 minutes remaining
and the volume is not really that good.
Now, for the big question, is it
possible to trade with 0.1 Solana in
today's market? And my answer to that is
yes, but you have to be very cautious on
what you buy. Number one thing you're
going to look out for is if the coin is
memeable. The reason why we managed to
dodge all the vamps was because this is
meme coins after all. Only memes will
send. Anyways, boys, that is going to be
it for the video. In 1 hour, we were
able to take our 0.1 Solana all the way
up to 0.245.
Now, once you make it to a level like
this, what I want you to do is de-risk a
little bit per buy. Instead of full
porting now, you guys need to only buy
with 0.05 or 0.07 Solana. So, you give
yourself at least three or four chances
to make it all back even if you take a
bad trade. All right, that is going to
be it for the video. If you want to
learn more about how to trade with 0.1
Solana, click the video on your screen
right now. It is a full detailed guide
that will guide you through how to grow
a small portfolio. Anyways, thank you so
much for watching. I love you all. See
you in the next one. Bye-bye.